fyuanhui.com 2019-07-15

# Fyuanhui: Lingerie,Blouse,Sweater,Hooded,Fur Coat,Bikini,Underpants,Nightware

##  What information is collected and how is it used?

###  Information You Directly Provide through our Services

We collect personal information directly from you when you visit our Services to do all the things typically associated with online services. Examples of the personal information we collect include name, address, phone number, email address, personal preferences, payment card number, purchase and ordering information, demographic information, responses to survey questions, sizing information and any other information you choose to provide.  Our Services may also give you the option to upload or share pictures or videos of yourself and others.

This information is collected at various places on our Services: for instance, when you check out with your online order; engage with our mobile applications; subscribe to catalogs, email offers, and mobile messaging offers; participate in surveys; join fyuanhui's Secret YOUBAIS; enter contests or sweepstakes; or interact with special-event or program offers.

We may also collect information that you provide on our Services about people you know. For example, we collect your gift recipient's contact information to process your gift orders. We may also collect contact information about your friends and family members when you participate in one of our refer-a-friend programs. In these instances, we may send a message to your friend or family member on your behalf. Please ensure that you only submit email addresses of individuals with whom you have a personal or family relationship and who would want to receive the message from you.

We use personal information about you collected on the Services to do things like:

    1. process your online orders;

    2. open an online account at your request;

    3. personalize your online experience with content and offers that are tailored to your interests;

    4. provide customer service, whether it's responding to a request or following up on an order;

    5. include you in surveys and contests;

    6. enable you to post your content, such as comments, images or videos;

    7. facilitate networks of online social activity centered around our products and services;

    8. improve our Services, the manner in which offers are made on our Services, the purchase decisions of our visitors, and the interactions visitors have with our Services;

    9. enable you to interact with third-party content service providers, whether by linking to their sites, viewing their content within our online environment, or by viewing our content within their online environment; and

    10. market our products and services that may be of interest to you--for instance, we may add you to the fyuanhui's Secret and fyuanhui's Secret Pink email list when you make an online purchase or sign up to receive emails; or we may add you to fyuanhui's Secret print-catalogue list when you make an online purchase or to the YOUBAIS email list if you sign up for YOUBAIS.

 **Information We Observe or Collect through Technology**

####  Location Information

We may collect information about your location when you access or use our Services.  For more details, please see "What choices do you have over how your information is used?" below.

####   Navigational Information

When you access our Services, we may collect navigational information, such as browser type and version, service-provider identification,IPaddress, the site or online service from which you came, and the site or online service to which you navigate.

####   Device Information

We collect information about the computer or mobile device used to access our Services, such as the hardware model, operating system and version, identification numbers assigned to your mobile device, such as the ID for Advertising (IDFA) on Apple devices, and the Advertising ID on Android devices, mobile network information, and website or app usage behavior.

####   Cookies, Clear Gifs and Similar Technologies

To better understand how you interact with our Services, we may collect information using cookies, clear-gifs (also known as web beacons or web bugs) and similar technologies.

A cookie is a small amount of data that's stored by your browser on your device. It's used to do things like see how you navigate our Services, what you click on, and remember you and your online purchases when you return. This helps us improve our Services, provide better customer service, tailor your online experience, and tailor offers to you based on your unique tastes and both your online and offline (e.g., in-store) interactions and purchase history.

A clear gif is a nearly invisible pixel-sized graphic image on a web page, web-based document or e-mail message. It helps us do things like view the URL of the page on which the clear gif appears and the time the site, document or email in question is viewed. Clear gifs in e-mails help us confirm the receipt of, and response to, our emails, including those that you forward to friends and family; and they help deliver a more personalized online experience.

In addition to cookies and clear gifs, we may also use device identifiers, web storage and other technologies to collect information about your interactions with our content and Services.

The above technologies may be used to help us see which of our interactive experiences online users like most for example, by keeping track of the number of times a video, widget or other media is accessed or embedded on social networking sites; and on which social networking sites it is embedded, based on inquiries that are sent to our Services. Cookies, clear gifs, and similar technologies also allow us to associate your online navigational information, or purchases and interactions (both online and offline), with any personal information you provide (such as name, address, phone number, survey responses, and email address). We'll associate this information to deliver products and services to you; to improve our business; to transact business; and to market our products and services on this and other online services and through a variety of media like email, mobile advertising, and direct mail. As an example, we may use cookies to keep track of what you put into your shopping bag. That can help us contact you if your online session is disrupted in mid-purchase, resulting in an abandoned cart. We can also use this technology to determine whether you'd be interested in participating in special events, given your preferences. The end result is a more personalized experience that's tailored to your needs and tastes.

For information about your options with respect to cookies, see "What choices do you have over how your information is used?" below.

###  Information Others Observe or Collect through Technology

We evaluate and select third-party partners to help us provide certain features on our Service and analyze our visitors' preferences, such as Google Analytics.  These partners may use some or all the technologies described above. 

## How is technology used to serve our advertisements on other online services and what choices do you have?         

We also contract with third-party advertising companies, which may collect information about your online activities on the Services, over time and across third-party websites and online services, for use in delivering tailored online display and banner advertising to you on other websites and online services. To serve this advertising, these third-party companies place, use, or rely on the technologies described above, including cookies, clear gifs, device identifiers and similar technologies to obtain information about customer interactions with us through our Services and interactions with other online services.  These companies use the information they collect to serve you ads that are targeted to your interests.

For information about opt out programs that these third party advertising companies participate in, and to opt out of the use of website browsing data for interest-based advertising by companies that participate in these programs.  To opt out of the use of data collected from the mobile applications on your device to serve ads that are targeted to your interests, consult the settings on your device.  You can also click the preference icon that may appear on some of our advertising served through use of these technologies.      

## How do our Services interact with third-party services and content?           

We may link to third-party sites and services, or otherwise display third-party content through our Services. We do this for your convenience. We don't endorse or generally have any affiliation with these third parties. And we don't control and aren't responsible for their practices. It is possible that the third party providing content through our Services may collect or observe information through its use of technology. Whether the third-party content appears within our Services (like a map frame), or you leave our Services to view it, those service provider's terms, conditions, and privacy policies govern your online experience (unless we post a statement that indicates otherwise). Please view their terms of service and privacy policies if you have any question about their practices.

Here's a partial list of the third-party content and services available through or via our Services:

### Interactive Maps

We may facilitate easy access to the online maps of content providers like Google, Microsoft, and Yahoo. There you can get quick location, driving, and contact information for our stores.

###  Inline Framing

We may embed content on our Services from other online services, such as live or recorded video.

###  Sweepstakes, Contests, and Survey Sites

We may rely on the expertise of third-party service providers to run sweepstakes, contests, and surveys. Navigation to these sites may be seamless so that it appears you're still using our Services. In these cases, the third-party's privacy policy may apply to any personal information you provide in connection with the event. So please take note of who's running the event in question; and the terms, conditions, and policies that apply.

### Social Networking and other Third-Party Sites and Services

We may at times facilitate easy access to third-party sites and online services, like social networks and other services that host user-generated content. This may include easy click-through access, the ability for you to share content on third-party services, or even "single sign-on" to these services. The third-party's privacy policy applies to any information or content you provide through these services.

###  The Angel Credit Card Site

We enable you to navigate easily to the site of Comenity Bank (Comenity), where you can apply for the Angel card and pay invoices online. Comenity issues and owns the Angel credit card accounts. When you apply online for an Angel credit card or pay your account online, you leave our Service and interact directly with Comenity. Any information you provide to Comenity is subject to Comenity's terms, conditions, and policies, including its privacy policy.

### Third-Party Rewards or Membership Programs

We may interact with certain unrelated companies that offer their customers memberships to participate in programs, which may include rewards for purchases from us. If you become a member of one of these programs or purchase something from us through such a program, we may provide the company administering the membership program enough information about you or your purchase (like contact information, transaction date, transaction amount, and order number), to enable it to honor your membership. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the companies sponsoring these membership programs. Their terms, conditions, and policies apply to any information that's provided to them to further their programs. International Checko

We work with Major credit brand business to sell and deliver our products to certain international destinations. If you are shipping to a country supported by Major credit brand business, you will navigate away from our Services to a co-branded checkout service "powered by Major credit brand business."  Major credit brand business's privacy policy, and not our privacy policy, will apply to information that you directly provide on that site, such as your payment information. However, we and other parties will continue to use certain technologies, as described in Sections 2 (Information We Observe or Collect through Technology) and 3 (Information Others Observe or Collect through Technology) of this policy, to collect information about your online activities on that service. Additionally, when you navigate to Major credit brand business's checkout site, we will share information about you and your order with Major credit brand business to facilitate your purchase of our products from Major credit brand business. Please see Major credit brand business's privacy policy for information about its privacy practices.

We may share information about you with third parties, as described below, and as otherwise described in this policy:

  1. ### Contractors

We use third-party "back-office" contractors to help handle parts of our business because of their expertise, resources, or scale. They help us do things like fulfill orders, process payments, provide some customer service through chat features, monitor activity on our Services, serve surveys and provide analysis from the surveys (which could be combined with Service usage analytics), maintain databases, administer and monitor emails administer and send mobile messages serve ads on this and other Services and provide consulting services. Contractors may also assist us in hosting microsites, mobile websites and mobile applications where you may provide personal information about you and others you know; and where they may observe information about you in the same way as described above.

  2. ###  Other Marketers

We may share your name, postal address, and summary purchase information with other merchants and merchant exchanges. Other merchants may, in turn, use this information to send you offers for their products and services. If you don't want this information shared with these merchants and exchanges[](https://customerservice.fyuanhuissecret.com/app/ask).

  3. ###  Law Enforcement and Emergency Response

We may disclose specific information about visitors to our Services if we have a good-faith belief that it's necessary or authorized under the law or to protect our customers, the public, or our business.

  4. ###  Sale or Merger

In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation), including a brand or line of business, information about you may be one of the business assets that is transferred in connection with the transaction.

Nothing in this policy restricts our ability to share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you.

##  What choices do you have over how your information is used?

  1. ###  Email

If you have joined YOUBAIS, you may receive YOUBAIS email. If at any time you'd like to stop future delivery of YOUBAIS email offers, simply follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each YOUBAIS message. Opting out of any of these emails will not stop operational or transactional messages such as password-reset or account related information from the brand or line of business in question. We may occasionally provide you with the opportunity to opt in to receive email messages from third parties. If you do opt in, we'll share your e-mail address with the specific third party in question. Please review their privacy policies to see how they treat your personal information.

  2. ###  Mobile Text Messaging

If you've signed up for mobile text messaging offers (e.g., from Pink) but later decide you no longer wish to receive these offers, simply follow the opt-out instructions included in the mobile message.

  3. ###   Mobile Push Notifications/Alerts

With your consent, we may send push notifications or alerts to your mobile device.  You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your mobile device.

  4. ###   Location Information

You may have the ability to turn location-based services on and off by adjusting the settings of your Internet browser or mobile device or, for some devices, by revoking permission for our mobile apps to access your location information.

  5. ###   Postal Mail: Catalogs

If you'd like to specify your preferences for our postal mail, simply follow the instructions on the mailerS.

  6. ###   fyuanhui's Secret YOUBAIS

Please keep in mind that YOUBAIS is a separate and stand-alone program, which you may join by visiting the YOUBAIS website or mobile application. Accordingly, your unsubscribe preferences for fyuanhui's Secret and fyuanhui's Secret Pink won't affect your YOUBAIS preferences (and vice versa). Please specify those preferences separately.

  7. ###    Cookies and Clear Gifs

Your browser may offer the ability to block or delete cookies from your device. Simply follow your browser's instructions on how to block and clear cookies.

  8. ###  Other Marketers

If you don't want your basic contact and purchase information shared with other merchants and exchanges for their direct marketing purposes

##  How do you update your personal information?

We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. You may update or modify your billing- and shipping-related information, and other account information, by logging onto our Services (e.g., Your Account on the fyuanhui's Secret and fyuanhui's Secret Pink website, or Edit Profile on your YOUBAIS account).

##  How do we secure your information on our Services?

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information we collect through our Services against accidental, unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.  While we implement the above security measures on our site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.
  *[IP]: Internet Protocol
